<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<testimonials>
  <testimonial>
    <name>
      Gibson Family      
    </name>
    <description>
      We think you handled all of our concerns &amp; questions very professionally &amp; with compassion. The monument was done exactly as we requested with excellent workmanship.
    </description>
    <image>
      
    </image>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <name>
      Hersh Family
    </name>
    <description>
      Great workmanship, great service and great people to deal with. We highly recommend their services.
    </description>
    <image>

    </image>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <name>
      Fodero Family
    </name>
    <description>
      Picking out a monument is not an easy task but you were very comforting to me &amp; you did a beautiful job &amp; in a timely manner.
    </description>
    <image>

    </image>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <name>
      Deiter Family
    </name>
    <description>
      The monument turned out just as I envisioned it. The workmanship is beautiful. We’re very happy with the results.
    </description>
    <image>

    </image>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <name>
      England Family
    </name>
    <description>
      Thank you for making, what is a very difficult process, so easy &amp; comforting. Your workmanship is excellent.
    </description>
    <image>

    </image>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <name>
      Mrs. Goll
    </name>
    <description>
      Thank you so much for your work on my husband’s monument. Your workmanship was truly top notch. My family was very happy with the way it turned out. We will recommend you to anyone in need of your services.
    </description>
    <image>
      goll.png
    </image>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <name>
      Mrs. Stephens
    </name>
    <description>
      A work of art! Thank you for my husband’s perfect monument. A tribute to his life’s achievements.
    </description>
    <image>

    </image>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <name>
      Wales Family
    </name>
    <description>
      Thank you for making this a pleasant experience. We are thrilled with the wonderful job you did. Thank you so much!
    </description>
    <image>

    </image>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <name>
      Booth Family
    </name>
    <description>
      Thank you so much for your patience and thoughtfulness throughout this process. We are very glad we came to you for our son’s monument. You did a beautiful job.
    </description>
    <image>

    </image>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <name>
      Mr. Ward
    </name>
    <description>
      We are very pleased with the finished product. It is just a beautiful piece of workmanship. Thank you for being so helpful. It was a pleasure to do business with you.
    </description>
    <image>

    </image>
  </testimonial>
</testimonials>